import type { Question } from "./state";

// Comment here
export const questions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: "born",
    worth: 100,
    category: "Before You Met Me",
    answerText: "Dallas",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "Where was I born?",
  },
  {
    id: "band",
    worth: 400,
    category: "Before You Met Me",
    answerText: "Percussion",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What did I play in band?",
  },
  {
    id: "dorm",
    worth: 200,
    category: "Before You Met Me",
    answerText: "Virginia Snider",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What dorm did I live in?",
  },
  {
    id: "dorm",
    worth: 300,
    category: "Before You Met Me",
    answerText: "Practicing Wheelies",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "I spent 6+ hours a day doing this during quarantine",
  },
  {
    id: "sport",
    worth: 500,
    category: "Before You Met Me",
    answerText: "Swimming",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What was my longest running sport I played as a child?",
  },
  {
    id: "fav-artist",
    worth: 200,
    category: "Music",
    answerText: "Jane Remover",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "Who is my favorite music artist?",
  },
  {
    id: "first-concert",
    worth: 300,
    category: "Music",
    answerText: "Travis Scott",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What was my first concert?",
  },
  {
    id: "fav-album",
    worth: 400,
    category: "Music",
    answerText: "Call Me If You Get Lost",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What is my favorite album of all time?",
  },
  {
    id: "fav-color",
    worth: 200,
    category: "Misc.",
    answerText: "Blue",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What is my favorite color? (Double points: explain why)",
  },
  {
    id: "fav-color",
    worth: 200,
    category: "Misc.",
    answerText: "Ramen Noodles",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What is my favorite night time meal?",
  },
  {
    id: "stemify",
    worth: 400,
    category: "Misc.",
    answerText: "Stemify",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText:
      "My creation of this website lead me to work for disgraced neo-nazi Kanye West the summer after freshman year.",
  },

  // Employment
  {
    id: "first-job",
    worth: 200,
    category: "Resume",
    answerText: "Picassos Pizza / Phone Operator",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What was my first job?",
  },
  {
    id: "on-campus-job",
    worth: 300,
    category: "Resume",
    answerText: "IT Help Desk",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What was my first on campus job?",
  },
  {
    id: "Current Company",
    worth: 400,
    category: "Resume",
    answerText: "Trieve",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText: "What is the name of the company I currently work for?",
  },
  {
    id: "bobo",
    worth: 500,
    category: "Resume",
    answerText: "Chicken Fried Rice",
    isAnswered: false,
    questionText:
      "I quit my job at Marble Slab on the spot when someone took a bite of my ______ without asking.",
  },
];
